Guide to the Irving McNeil Ives papers, 1862-1958
Ives, Irving McNeil papers, 1862-1958
- SERIES I. CORRESPONDENCE and LEGISLATION
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Hydro-Electric Redevelopment.] Hearings - Niagara Power Project - 1951, 1953, 1955 (Box 228, Folder 20)
    electricity (power production)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Hydro-Electric Power Redevelopment.] Niagara Brief - 1956 (Box 228, Folder 21)
    electricity (power production); Power Authority - State of N. Y.
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Niagara Hydro-Electric Power Redevelopment.] Miscellaneous - I - 1953-1956 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    electricity (power production); Robert Moses, John E. Burton; Rochester Gas and Electric
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Niagara Hydro-Electric Power Redevelopment.] Miscellaneous - II - 1954-1956 (Box 229, Folder 2)
    electricity (power production), Niagara Power Development or Power Development N. Y. S.; William E. Miller, Paul Martin
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Niagara Hydro-Electric Power Redevelopment.] Miscellaneous - III - 1953, 1956-1957 (Box 229, Folder 3)
    electricity (power production), rivers and harbors (improvement); Joseph F. Clark, Jacob Javits, Robert Moses
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Allegany River (Olean-Salamanca) - Flood Control - 1947-1952 (Box 229, Folder 4)
    Department of the Army Corps of Engineers
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Canaseraga Creek - Flood Control - 1952-1956 (Box 229, Folder 5)
    U. S. Army Corps of Engineers
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Copake Falls - Flood Control - 1955 (Box 229, Folder 6)
    Department of the Army, Office of Chief of Engineers, Columbia County Bd. of Supervisors
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Dean Creek Watershed - 1953 (Box 229, Folder 7)
    W. Sterling Cole, Rodmann Fellows, U. S. Dept. of Agriculture
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Fire Island Inlet - 1947-1956 (Box 229, Folder 8)
    rivers and harbors (improvement); Corps of Engineers, U. S. Army, Long Island Association, Fire Island Inlet Committee
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Hoosick River Watershed - 1953-1954 (Box 229, Folder 9)
    flood control; U. S. Dept. of Agriculture
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Jones Inlet - Correspondence - 1946-1951 (Box 229, Folder 10)
    rivers and harbors (improvement)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Jones Inlet - General Information - 1950-1951 (Box 229, Folder 11)
    rivers and harbors (improvement); Herbert H. Lehman, Leonard W. Hall, Robert Moses
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Lake Champlain Waterway - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 12)
    rivers and harbors (improvement); James A. Fitzpatrick
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Monkey Run Creek Flood Control project - 1948-1954 (Box 229, Folder 13)
    William F. Knowland, William C. Decker, Horace S. Evans; Dept. of the Army, Office of the Chief of Eingineers. City of Corning
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Mt. Upton Impact Study - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 14)
    public works; Citizens Comm. to Oppose the Mt. Upton Dam
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Mt. Upton - Unadilla Valley Dam ?Correspondence - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Mt. Upton - Unadilla Valley Dam ?Correspondence (Form letters) - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Mt. Upton - Unadilla Valley Dam ?Miscellaneous - 1952 - 1946-1952 (Box 229, Folder 17)
    flood control; U. S. Army, Corps of Engineers
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Unadilla Dam - 1951 - 1950-1953 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    flood control; Janet Hill Gordon; Chenango County Bd. of Supervisors
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Niagara Falls Canal - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 19-20)
    rivers and harbors (improvement); Very Rev. Francis L. Meade, C. M.
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Ogdensburg Bridge - [1955] (Box 229, Folder 21)
    bridges (N. Y. S.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Oneida Lake - 19-- (Box 229, Folder 22)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Richelieu Canal - 1952 (Box 229, Folder 23)
    rivers and harbors (improvement); James A. Fitzpatrick, L. W. Byrne
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] St. Lawrence Canal - 1948 (Box 229, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Salmon River - River Dredging - 1950-1953 (Box 229, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Saw Mill River - 1947-1948 (Box 229, Folder 26)
    flood control; U. S. War Department, Office of the Chief of Engineers
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Scajaquada Creek - Flood Control - 1947 (Box 229, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Skinner Creek, Mannsville - Flood Control - 1948-1951 (Box 229, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Steinway Creek Astoria, N. Y. Improvement - 1948, 1949 (Box 229, Folder 29)
    U. S. Department of the Army, Board of Engineers for Rivers and Harbors
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Stony Island Harbor (Lake Ontario) - Snowshoe Bay - Henderson Harbor - 1948 (Box 229, Folder 30)
    flood control; Claude H. Dunk
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Tonawanda Creek - Bastavita and vicinity flood control - 1947-1951, 1954 (Box 229, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] West Corners, Endicott area - Flood control - 1948 (Box 229, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] West Chester Creek - 1950 (Box 229, Folder 33)
    flood control; U. S. Army Corps of Engineers
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Public Works.] Whitney Point Reservoir Clearing Flood Protection Otselic River - 1950 (Box 229, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Military Academy - Correspondence - 1948-1952 (Box 230, Folder 1)
    U. S. Military Academy (appts.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Military Academy - Correspondence - 1958 (Box 230, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Naval Academy - Correspondence - 1948-1955 (Box 230, Folder 3)
    U. S. Naval Academy (appts.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Naval Academy - Correspondence - 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 4)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Air Force Academy - Correspondence - 1958 (Box 230, Folder 5)
    U. S. Air Force Academy (appts.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] United States Merchant Marine Academy - Correspondence - 1958 (Box 230, Folder 6)
    U. S. Merchant Marine Academy (appts.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] U. S. Civil Service Examinations - 1947-1949 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    U. S. Service Academies (appts.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Civil Service Results and blanks - 1949-1955 (Box 230, Folder 8)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academy Appointments.] U. S. Civil Service Comm. - Correspondence - 1953-1958 (Box 230, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academy Appointments.] Civil Service Arrangements - 7/51 for 1952 Admission - 1951 (Box 230, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Civil Service Arrangements for Naval Academy Exam - 7/14/52 for 1953 admission - 1952-1953 (Box 230, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] 1959 Air Force Academy appts. - 1956-1958 (Box 230, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] 1959 Merchant Marine Academy Candidates - 1958 (Box 230, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] 1959 Military Academy appts. - 1956-1958 (Box 230, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] News releases - I.M.I. - re service academy appts. - 1958 (Box 230, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academy Appointments.] Nominating blanks - 1957 (Box 230, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academy Appointments.] Sample Questions, etc. - Civil Service - 19-- (Box 230, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Robert Brogi - Class of 1962 - 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 18)
    U. S. Military Academy (appt.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] George Scott Eaton ?Class of 1962 - 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 19)
    U. S. Air Force Academy (appt.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Peter H. Foster - Class of 1959 - West Point - 1954-1958 (Box 230, Folder 20)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Leonard Henderson - Class of 1967 - 1952-1958 (Box 230, Folder 21)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] James John, Jr. Henry ?Class of 1960 - 1955-1958 (Box 230, Folder 22)
    U. S. Naval Academy (appt.)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Clarence Hilbert - Class of 1959 - 1954-1958 (Box 230, Folder 23)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Salim J. Kanakry - Class of 1960 - 1954-1956 (Box 230, Folder 24)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Richard Madden - Class of 1962 - 1957-1959 (Box 230, Folder 25)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Michael T. Newell - Class of 1962 - 1956-1958 (Box 230, Folder 26)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Roger Alan Nichols - Class of 1959 - Annapolis - 1953-1955 (Box 230, Folder 27)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] James H. Van Ornum - Class of 1962 - 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 28)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] Frederick P. Wilson - Class of 1962 - 1956-1958 (Box 230, Folder 29)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies.] John M. Wood III - Class of 1962 - 1957-1958 (Box 230, Folder 30)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Service Academies, 1948-1958.] Lemuel G. Wright, Jr. - 1952-1958 (Box 230, Folder 31)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Sponsorships] List of sponsorships for 1950, 1951, and 1952 campaign - 1950-1952 (Box 230, Folder 32)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] All American Defense Assoc. (sponsorships) - 1950 (Box 230, Folder 33)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] American Christian Palestine Committee (sponsorships) - 1953-1958 (Box 230, Folder 34)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] American Israel society (sponsorships) - 1953-1958 (Box 230, Folder 35)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Sponsorships.] American Political Science Assoc. (2nd folder) - 1953-1954 (Box 230, Folder 36)
    scholarships
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Bard College (sponsorships) - 1954-1958 (Box 230, Folder 37)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] The Committee of One Million (sponsorships) - 1953-1958 (Box 230, Folder 38)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Empire State Music Festival (sponsorships) - 1955-1957 (Box 230, Folder 39)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Marine Corps League - (Kings County Council) sponsorships - 1948-1953 (Box 230, Folder 40)
    Charities (sponsorships); Marine Corps League
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Robert Porter Patterson Memorial Committee (sponsorships) - 1952-1953 (Box 230, Folder 41)
    Union College
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Sponsorships.] Yaune Hebrew Theological Seminary ?I.M.I. Scholarship Fund - 1957 (Box 230, Folder 42)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Sponsorships.] Messages, Requests for Contributions - 1946, 1954-1955 (Box 230, Folder 43)
    charities
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 80th - 1st - 1947 (Box 231, Folder 1)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 80th - 2nd - 1948 (Box 231, Folder 2)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] I.M.I. - Voting Record, 1947-1952 - (Compiled by Congressional Quarterly) - 1953-1954 - 1947-1953 (Box 231, Folder 3)
    I.M.I. (voting record)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Voting Record - I.M.I. - 80th - 82nd Congresses - 1947-1952 (Box 231, Folder 4)
    I.M.I. (voting record); Research Division. Republican National Comm.
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] Voting Record - 80th - 82nd Congresses - 1948-1952 (Box 231, Folder 5)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files.] I.M.I. - Voting Record, 1947-1952 - (Compiled by Congressional Quarterly) - 1953-1954 - 1948-1952 (Box 231, Folder 6)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 83rd - 1st - 1953 (Box 231, Folder 7)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 83rd - 2nd - 1954 (Box 231, Folder 8)
    U. S. Senate (voting record)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 84th - 1st - 1955 (Box 231, Folder 9)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 84th - 2nd - 1956 (Box 231, Folder 10)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 85th - 1st - 1957 (Box 231, Folder 11)
  - [U. S. Senate. Subject Files. Voting Record.] I.M.I. - 85th - 2nd - 1958 (Box 231, Folder 12)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements.] History of Policy Files - 19-- (Box 231, Folder 13)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congress Rec. 1948 - 1947 (Box 231, Folder 14)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congressional Record - 1948 (Box 231, Folder 15)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congressional Record - 1949 (Box 231, Folder 16)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Misc. Policy Statements - Policy suggestions Speeches and proposed speeches - Press Releases News Clippings. - 1949-1952 (Box 231, Folder 17)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congressional Record - 1950 (Box 231, Folder 18)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congressional Record - 1951 (Box 231, Folder 19)
  - [U. S. Senate. Policy Statements. Press Releases.] Releases for Press and Congressional Record - 1952 (Box 231, Folder 20)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Agriculture - File 1, Set 1 - 1948-1952 (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Civil Rights - File 2, Set 1 - 1948-1952 (Box 232, Folder 2)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Communism - subversive Activity - File 3, Set 1 - 1949-1952 (Box 232, Folder 3)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Controls - File 4, Set 1 - 1948-1952 (Box 232, Folder 4)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Economy in Government - File 5, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 5)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Foreign Relations - File 6, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 6)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Housing and Rent Control - File 7, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 7)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Government Organization and Operation - File 8, Set 1 - 1949-1952 (Box 232, Folder 8)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Government Regulation - File 9, Set 1 - 1947, 1949, 1952 (Box 232, Folder 9)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Immigration - Displaced Persons - File 10, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 10)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - File 11, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 11)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Miscellaneous - File 12, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 12)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - National Defense - File 13, Set 1 - 1948-1952 (Box 232, Folder 13)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Nominations - File 14, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 14)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Public Works - File 15, Set 1 - 1947-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 232, Folder 15)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Social Welfare - File 16, Set 1 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 16)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Taxation - File17, Set 1 - 1947-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 232, Folder 17)
    >
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Veterans - File 18, Set 1 - 1948-1949, 1951-1952 (Box 232, Folder 18)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Agriculture - File 1, Set 2 - 1948-1952 (Box 232, Folder 19)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Civil Rights - File 2, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 232, Folder 20)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Communism - File 3, Set 2 - 1949-1952 (Box 232, Folder 21)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Controls - File 4, Set 2 - 1948, 1950-1952 (Box 232, Folder 22)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Economy in Government - File 5, Set 2 - 1947, 1949-1952 (Box 232, Folder 23)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Foreign Relations - File 6, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 1)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Housing and Rent Control - File 7, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 2)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Government Organization and Operations - File 8, Set 2 - 1949-1952 (Box 233, Folder 3)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Government Regulations - File 9, Set 2 - 1947, 1949, 1952 (Box 233, Folder 4)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Immigration - Displaced Persons - File 10, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 5)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - File 11, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 6)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Miscellaneous - File 12, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 7)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - National Defense - File 13, Set 2 - 1948-1952 (Box 233, Folder 8)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Nominations - File 14, Set 2 - 1949-1952 (Box 233, Folder 9)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Public Works - File 15, Set 2 - 1947-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 233, Folder 10)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Social Welfare - File 16, Set 2 - 1947-1952 (Box 233, Folder 11)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements ?Taxation - File 17, Set 2 - 1947-1948, 1950-1952 (Box 233, Folder 12)
  - [1st Term.] Policy statements - Veterans - File 18, Set 2 - 1948-1949, 1951-1952 (Box 233, Folder 13)
  - [Policy Statements. 2nd Term.] I.M.I. - Committee and Biographical Data - 1952-1957 (Box 233, Folder 14)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Agriculture - 2nd term - File 1, Set 1 - 1954-1958 (Box 233, Folder 15)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Civil Rights - 2nd term - File 2, Set 1 - 1953-1957 (Box 233, Folder 16)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Communism - 2nd term - File 3, Set 1 - 1953-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 233, Folder 17)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Controls - 2nd term - File 4, Set 1 - 1953, 1956 (Box 233, Folder 18)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Appropriations (Econ. In Govt.) - 2nd term - File 5, Set 1 - 1953, 1955-1958 (Box 233, Folder 19)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Foreign Relations - 2nd term - File 6, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 20)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Organization and Operation - 2nd term - File 7, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 21)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Regulations - 2nd term - File 8, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 22)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Housing and Rent Control - 2nd term - File 9, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 23)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Immigration - 2nd term - File 10, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 233, Folder 24)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 2nd term - File 11, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 1)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 2nd term - File 11, Section 2, Set 1 - 1958 (Box 234, Folder 2)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Miscellaneous - 2nd term - File 12, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 3)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - National Defense - 2nd term - File 13, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 4)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Nominations - 2nd term - File 14, Set 1 - 1953-1956, 1958 (Box 234, Folder 5)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Public Works - 2nd term - File 15, Set 1 - 1953-1954, 1956-1958 (Box 234, Folder 6)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Social Welfare - 2nd term - File 16, Set 1 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 7)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Taxation - 2nd term - File 17, Set 1 - 1953-1954, 1957-1958 (Box 234, Folder 8)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Veterans - 2nd term - File 18, Set 1 - 1953-1954, 1957 (Box 234, Folder 9)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Agriculture - 1953 - File 1, Set 2 - 1954, 1956-1958 (Box 234, Folder 10)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements ?Civil Rights - 2nd term - File 2, Set 2 - 1953-1957 (Box 234, Folder 11)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Communism - 1953 - File 3, Set 2 - 1953-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 234, Folder 12)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Controls - 1953 - File 4, Set 2 - 1953, 1956 (Box 234, Folder 13)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Appropriations (Econ. In Govt.) - 2nd term - File 5, Set 2 - 1953, 1955-1958 (Box 234, Folder 14)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Foreign Relations - 1953 - File 6, Set 2 - 1955-1958 (Box 234, Folder 15)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Organization and Operation - 2nd term - File 7, Set 2 - 1956-1958 (Box 234, Folder 16)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Regulations - File 8, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 17)
  - 2nd Term.] Policy statements - Housing and Rent Control - 2nd term - File 9, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 18)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Immigration - 1953 - File 10, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 19)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 1953 - File 11, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 20)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 2nd term - File 11, Section 2, Set 2 - 1958 (Box 234, Folder 21)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Miscellaneous - 1953 - File 12, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 234, Folder 22)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - National Defense - 1953 - File 13, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 1)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements ?Nominations - 1953 - File 14, Set 2 - 1953-1956, 1958 (Box 235, Folder 2)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Public Works - 1953 - File 15, Set 2 - 1953-1954, 1956-1958 (Box 235, Folder 3)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Social Welfare Legislation - 1953 - File 16, Set 2 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 4)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Taxation - 1953 - File 17, Set 2 - 1953-1954, 1957-1958 (Box 235, Folder 5)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Veterans - 2nd term - File 18, Set 2 - 1953-1954, 1958 (Box 235, Folder 6)
  - [2nd Term.] I.M.I. - Committee and Biographical Data - Set 3 - 1952, 1954, 1956-1957 (Box 235, Folder 7)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Agriculture - 2nd term - File 1, Set 3 - 1952-1958 (Box 235, Folder 8)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Civil Rights - 2nd term - File 2, Set 3 - 1953-1957 (Box 235, Folder 9)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Communism - 2nd term - File 3, Set 3 - 1953-1954, 1956-1957 (Box 235, Folder 10)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Controls - 2nd term - File 4, Set 5 - 1953, 1956 (Box 235, Folder 11)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Appropriations - 2nd term - File 5a, Set 6 - 1953, 1955-1958 (Box 235, Folder 12)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Foreign Relations - 2nd term - File 6, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 13)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Organization and Operation - 2nd term - File 7, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 14)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Government Regulations - 2nd term - File 8, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 15)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Housing and Rent Control - 2nd term - File 9, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 16)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Immigration - 2nd term - File 10, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 17)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 2nd term - File 11, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 18)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Labor Relations - 2nd term - File 11, Set 2, Set 3 - 1958 (Box 235, Folder 19)
  - [2nd Term.] Policy statements - Miscellaneous - 2nd term - File 12, Set 3 - 1953-1958 (Box 235, Folder 20)